mysocialbook.com 2014-07-24

# Privacy policy

This privacy policy describes how My Social Book uses and protects any information that is collected about our users. This document describes exactly what information is collected, how it is safeguarded, and how you can control the way it is used.

My Social Book is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask for any personal information, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

My Social Book may change this policy from time to time, and the latest version will be available on this page. 

## Long-term usage - User database

We collect the following information :

  * Facebook Name and unique ID
  * Customer information such as email, postal address
  * Customer orders

We may use this information for one or more of the following reasons:

  * To send you our latest information
  * Internal record keeping
  * Improving our products and services
  * Security

## Temporary usage - Product generation

For the production of our product and the real-time book quote, we gather a lot of information from your Facebook account, such as :

  * All posted content (statuses, pictures, ...)
  * All the comments
  * The checkins
  * Your friend list
  * Photo albums

We use the temporary data to give you a real time quote and preview of your products. All the source data is destroyed automatically after a few days. If you make an order, we keep the resulting book only during the lifetime of your order

We are committed to the security of any information that we hold. We have put in industry standard safeguards to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure to your personal information.

For more information contact us at: [help@mysocialbook.com](mailto:help@mysocialbook.com)
